<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Manifest xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="CSUManifest.xsd" CSUVersion="1.0">
    <UpdateID>17.3</UpdateID>
    <OwningChannel>AdobeIllustrator17-mul_x64</OwningChannel>
    <TargetBuildType>2</TargetBuildType>
	<TargetLicensingType>1</TargetLicensingType>
	<RecommendingChannels>
		<ChannelID>AdobeIllustrator17-mul_x64</ChannelID>
	</RecommendingChannels>
    <DisplayName default="en_US">
        <en_US>Adobe Illustrator CC Update (version 17.1.0) x64</en_US>
		<en_GB>Adobe Illustrator CC Update (version 17.1.0) x64</en_GB>
        <cs_CZ>Adobe Illustrator CC - aktualizace (verze 17.1.0) x64</cs_CZ>
        <da_DK>Adobe Illustrator CC – opdatering (version 17.1.0) x64</da_DK>
        <de_DE>Adobe Illustrator CC-Aktualisierung (Version 17.1.0) x64</de_DE>
        <es_ES>Actualización de Adobe Illustrator CC (versión 17.1.0) x64</es_ES>
		<es_MX>Actualización de Adobe Illustrator CC (versión 17.1.0) x64</es_MX>
        <fr_FR>Mise à jour d'Adobe Illustrator CC (version 17.1.0) x64</fr_FR>
		<fr_CA>Mise à jour d'Adobe Illustrator CC (version 17.1.0) x64</fr_CA>
		<fr_MA>Mise à jour d'Adobe Illustrator CC (version 17.1.0) x64</fr_MA>
		<fi_FI>Adobe Illustrator CC Update (version 17.1.0) x64</fi_FI>
        <hu_HU>Adobe Illustrator CC frissítés (17.1.0 verzió) x64</hu_HU>
        <it_IT>Aggiornamento Adobe Illustrator CC (versione 17.1.0) x64</it_IT>
        <ja_JP>Adobe Illustrator CC アップデート (バージョン 17.1.0) x64</ja_JP>
        <ko_KR>Adobe Illustrator CC 업데이트(버전 17.1.0) x64</ko_KR>
        <nl_NL>Adobe Illustrator CC-update (versie 17.1.0) x64</nl_NL>
        <pl_PL>Adobe Illustrator CC — uaktualnienie (wersja 17.1.0) x64</pl_PL>
        <pt_BR>Atualização do Adobe Illustrator CC (Versão 17.1.0) x64</pt_BR>
        <ru_RU>Обновление Adobe Illustrator CC (версия 17.1.0) x64</ru_RU>
        <sv_SE>Adobe Illustrator CC-uppdatering (version 17.1.0) x64</sv_SE>
        <tr_TR>Adobe Illustrator CC Güncellemesi (sürüm 17.1.0) x64</tr_TR>
        <uk_UA>Оновлення Adobe Illustrator CC (версія 17.1.0) x64</uk_UA>
        <zh_CN>Adobe Illustrator CC 更新（版本 17.1.0） x64</zh_CN>
        <zh_TW>Adobe Illustrator CC 更新 (版本 17.1.0) x64</zh_TW>
		<en_AE>Adobe Illustrator CC Update (version 17.1.0) x64</en_AE>
		<en_IL>Adobe Illustrator CC Update (version 17.1.0) x64</en_IL>
    </DisplayName>
    <Description default="en_US">
		<en_US>Live Corners, All-new Pencil tool, Path Segment Reshape, Typekit integration, Windows 7 &amp; 8 HiDPI support, Windows 8 enhanced touch and pressure-sensitive drawing support, Custom Tools panel, Settings import and export. Additional enhancements: Layer states remembered, ability to draw and resize artboard from center, modify perspective grid and artwork updates to match, access fill/stroke controls in Swatches panel, sliders to control opacity settings, option for creating responsive SVG files, pixel-aligned round-tripping of SVG files, and more. Fixes include: Alt/Option + scroll for zoom on Mac, preservation of layer structure when exporting DWG files, keyboard shortcuts work when using the Apple Magic Mouse.</en_US>
		<en_GB>Live Corners, All-new Pencil tool, Path Segment Reshape, Typekit integration, Windows 7 &amp; 8 HiDPI support, Windows 8 enhanced touch and pressure-sensitive drawing support, Custom Tools panel, Settings import and export. Additional enhancements: Layer states remembered, ability to draw and resize artboard from center, modify perspective grid and artwork updates to match, access fill/stroke controls in Swatches panel, sliders to control opacity settings, option for creating responsive SVG files, pixel-aligned round-tripping of SVG files, and more. Fixes include: Alt/Option + scroll for zoom on Mac, preservation of layer structure when exporting DWG files, keyboard shortcuts work when using the Apple Magic Mouse.</en_GB>
        <cs_CZ>Živé rohy, zcela nový nástroj Tužka, změna tvaru segmentu cesty, integrace služby Typekit, podpora HiDPI v systémech Windows 7 &amp; 8, vylepšená podpora dotekového a tlakově citlivého kreslení ve Windows 8, vlastní panely nástrojů, import a export nastavení. Další rozšíření: stavy vrstev si lze pamatovat, schopnost kreslit a měnit velikost plátna ze středu, měnit perspektivní mřížku a aktualizace kresby tak, aby si odpovídaly, přistupovat k ovládacím prvkům výplně a tahu v panelu Vzorník, posuvníky pro nastavení průhlednosti, volba pro vytváření responsivních souborů SVG, úpravy souborů SVG s předáváním mezi aplikacemi se zarovnáním na obrazové body, a další. Mezi opravy patří: Alt/Option + otáčení kolečkem na systému Mac mění přiblížení, zachování struktury vrstvy při exportu DWG souborů, klávesové zkratky fungují i při používání Apple Magic Mouse.</cs_CZ>
        <da_DK>Live-hjørner, det helt nye Blyant-værktøj, omformning af kurvesegmenter, Typekit-integration, understøttelse af HiDPI i Windows 7 og 8, forbedret understøttelse af berøring og trykfølsom tegning i Windows 8, panelet Brugerdefinerede værktøjer, import og eksport af indstillinger. Flere forbedringer: Lagtilstande huskes, det er muligt at tegne og ændre størrelsen på tegnebrættet fra midten, perspektivgitter og illustrationer kan ændres til at passe, du kan få adgang til fyld/streg-kontroller i panelet Farveprøver, skydere til kontrol af opacitetsindstillinger, mulighed for at oprette responsive SVG-filer, pixeljusteret round-tripping af SVG-filer, m.m. Rettelser omfatter: Alt/Option + rul for at zoome på Mac, bevaring af lagstruktur under eksport af DWG-filer, tastaturgenveje fungerer ved brug af Apple Magic Mouse.</da_DK>
        <de_DE>Interaktive Ecken, Neuer-Buntstift-Werkzeug, Formänderung für Pfadsegment, Typekit-Integration, Windows 7- &amp; 8-HiDPI-Unterstützung, Verbesserte berührungs- und druckempfindliche Zeichenunterstützung für Windows 8, Benutzerdefiniertes Werkzeugbedienfeld, Einstellungsimport und -export. Zusätzliche Verbesserungen: Speicherung der Ebenenstatus, Option zum Zeichnen auf und Skalieren einer Zeichenfläche von der Mitte aus, Ändern und Anpassen von Perspektivenrastern und Bildmaterial-Aktualisierungen, Zugriff auf Steuerungen für Flächen und Konturen im Farbfeldbedienfeld, Regler für die Deckkrafteinstellungen, Option zur Erstellung interaktiver SVG-Dateien, An Pixeln ausgerichteter Export von SVG-Dateien u. v. m. Problembehebungen beinhalten Folgendes: Alt-/Wahltaste + Scrollen für Zoom auf Mac-Systemen, Beibehaltung der Ebenenstrukturen beim Export von DWG-Dateien, Funktionierende Tastaturbefehle bei Verwendung der Magic Mouse von Apple.</de_DE>
        <es_ES>Vértices interactivos, una herramienta Lápiz completamente renovada, reforma de segmentos de trazado, integración de Typekit, compatibilidad con pantallas HiDPI en Windows 7 y 8, compatibilidad con el nuevo modo de dibujo sensible al tacto y a la presión de Windows 8, creación de paneles de herramientas personalizados, importación y exportación de la configuración. Mejoras adicionales: A partir de ahora, Illustrator recuerda el estado de las capas, puede dibujar y redimensionar las ilustraciones desde el centro, modificar la cuadrícula de perspectiva y actualizar las ilustraciones para hacerlas coincidir, acceder a los controles de relleno y trazado en el panel Muestras, se han incluido reguladores para ajustar la opacidad, una opción para crear archivos SVG flexibles, la posibilidad de crear contornos con alineación de píxeles en archivos SVG y mucho más. Entre las correcciones destacamos las siguientes: Alt/Opción + arrastrar para hacer zoom en Mac, conservación de la estructura de las capas al exportar archivos DWG y los métodos abreviados de teclado ya funcionan con el Magic Mouse de Apple.</es_ES>
		<es_MX>Vértices interactivos, una herramienta Lápiz completamente renovada, reforma de segmentos de trazado, integración de Typekit, compatibilidad con pantallas HiDPI en Windows 7 y 8, compatibilidad con el nuevo modo de dibujo sensible al tacto y a la presión de Windows 8, creación de paneles de herramientas personalizados, importación y exportación de la configuración. Mejoras adicionales: A partir de ahora, Illustrator recuerda el estado de las capas, puede dibujar y redimensionar las ilustraciones desde el centro, modificar la cuadrícula de perspectiva y actualizar las ilustraciones para hacerlas coincidir, acceder a los controles de relleno y trazado en el panel Muestras, se han incluido reguladores para ajustar la opacidad, una opción para crear archivos SVG flexibles, la posibilidad de crear contornos con alineación de píxeles en archivos SVG y mucho más. Entre las correcciones destacamos las siguientes: Alt/Opción + arrastrar para hacer zoom en Mac, conservación de la estructura de las capas al exportar archivos DWG y los métodos abreviados de teclado ya funcionan con el Magic Mouse de Apple.</es_MX>
		<fi_FI>Live Corners, All-new Pencil tool, Path Segment Reshape, Typekit integration, Windows 7 &amp; 8 HiDPI support, Windows 8 enhanced touch and pressure-sensitive drawing support, Custom Tools panel, Settings import and export. Additional enhancements: Layer states remembered, ability to draw and resize artboard from center, modify perspective grid and artwork updates to match, access fill/stroke controls in Swatches panel, sliders to control opacity settings, option for creating responsive SVG files, pixel-aligned round-tripping of SVG files, and more. Fixes include: Alt/Option + scroll for zoom on Mac, preservation of layer structure when exporting DWG files, keyboard shortcuts work when using the Apple Magic Mouse.</fi_FI>
        <fr_FR>angles dynamiques, tout nouvel outil Crayon, modelage des segments de tracé, intégration de Typekit, prise en charge des écrans haute résolution sous Windows 7 et 8, prise en charge de la fonctionnalité de dessin sensible à la pression et au toucher améliorée sous Windows 8, panneau Outils personnalisé, importation et exportation des paramètres. Améliorations supplémentaires : mémorisation des états de calque, possibilité de travailler et de redimensionner le plan de travail à partir du centre, modification de la grille de perspective et des mises à jour de l'illustration pour qu'elles correspondent, accès aux commandes de fond/contour via le panneau Nuancier, curseurs permettant de contrôler les paramètres d'opacité, option permettant de créer des fichiers SVG réactifs, allers-retours alignés sur les pixels pour les fichiers SVG et bien d'autres améliorations. Les corrections incluent : touche Alt/Option + défilement pour zoomer sous Mac, conservation de la structure de calques lors de l'exportation de fichiers DWG, fonctionnement des raccourcis clavier lors de l'utilisation de la souris Apple Magic Mouse.</fr_FR>
		<fr_CA>angles dynamiques, tout nouvel outil Crayon, modelage des segments de tracé, intégration de Typekit, prise en charge des écrans haute résolution sous Windows 7 et 8, prise en charge de la fonctionnalité de dessin sensible à la pression et au toucher améliorée sous Windows 8, panneau Outils personnalisé, importation et exportation des paramètres. Améliorations supplémentaires : mémorisation des états de calque, possibilité de travailler et de redimensionner le plan de travail à partir du centre, modification de la grille de perspective et des mises à jour de l'illustration pour qu'elles correspondent, accès aux commandes de fond/contour via le panneau Nuancier, curseurs permettant de contrôler les paramètres d'opacité, option permettant de créer des fichiers SVG réactifs, allers-retours alignés sur les pixels pour les fichiers SVG et bien d'autres améliorations. Les corrections incluent : touche Alt/Option + défilement pour zoomer sous Mac, conservation de la structure de calques lors de l'exportation de fichiers DWG, fonctionnement des raccourcis clavier lors de l'utilisation de la souris Apple Magic Mouse.</fr_CA>
		<fr_MA>angles dynamiques, tout nouvel outil Crayon, modelage des segments de tracé, intégration de Typekit, prise en charge des écrans haute résolution sous Windows 7 et 8, prise en charge de la fonctionnalité de dessin sensible à la pression et au toucher améliorée sous Windows 8, panneau Outils personnalisé, importation et exportation des paramètres. Améliorations supplémentaires : mémorisation des états de calque, possibilité de travailler et de redimensionner le plan de travail à partir du centre, modification de la grille de perspective et des mises à jour de l'illustration pour qu'elles correspondent, accès aux commandes de fond/contour via le panneau Nuancier, curseurs permettant de contrôler les paramètres d'opacité, option permettant de créer des fichiers SVG réactifs, allers-retours alignés sur les pixels pour les fichiers SVG et bien d'autres améliorations. Les corrections incluent : touche Alt/Option + défilement pour zoomer sous Mac, conservation de la structure de calques lors de l'exportation de fichiers DWG, fonctionnement des raccourcis clavier lors de l'utilisation de la souris Apple Magic Mouse.</fr_MA>
        <hu_HU>Élő sarkok, megújított Ceruza eszköz, Görbeszegmens átformálása, Typekit integráció, Windows 7 és 8 HiDPI-támogatás, Windows 8 továbbfejlesztett érintéses és nyomásérzékeny rajzolás támogatása, Egyéni eszközök panel, Beállítások importálása és exportálása. További fejlesztések: rétegállapotok megjegyzése, rajztábla rajzolása és átméretezése a középpontból kiindulva, prepektivarács és grafika frissítéseinek módosítása az egyezőséghez, hozzáférés a kitöltés/körvonal vezérlőihez a Színtárak panelen, csúszkák az opacitás beállításainak ellenőrzéséhez, érzékeny  SVG fájlok készítésének beállítása, SVG fájlok képpontigazított körbejárása, és mások. Javítások tartalma: Alt/Option + gögetés nagyításhoz Mac rendszeren, rétegszerkezet megőrzése DWG fájlok exportálásakor, a gyorsbillentyűk működnek Apple Magic Mouse használatakor.</hu_HU>
        <it_IT>Angoli dinamici, nuovo strumento Matita, rimodellazione dei segmenti di tracciato, integrazione Typekit, supporto per Windows 7 e 8 ad alta definizione, supporto migliorato in Windows 8 per funzioni touch e disegno sensibile alla pressione, pannello Strumenti personalizzato, importazione ed esportazione delle impostazioni. Ulteriori miglioramenti: memorizzazione degli stati dei livelli, possibilità di disegnare e ridimensionare la tavola di disegno dal centro, aggiornamento della grafica se si modifica la griglia prospettica, controlli di riempimento e traccia dal pannello Campioni, cursori per regolare le impostazioni di opacità, opzione per creare file SVG reattivi, allineamento pixel per flusso di lavoro completo con file SVG e molto altro. Le correzioni comprendono Alt/Opzione + scorrimento per lo zoom su Mac, rispetto della struttura dei livelli nell'esportazione di file DWG, scelte rapide da tastiera funzionanti con Apple Magic Mouse.</it_IT>
        <ja_JP>ライブコーナー、新しくなった鉛筆ツール、パスセグメントのリシェイプ、Typekit 統合、Windows 7 および 8 HiDPI サポート、Windows 8 向けに拡張されたタッチおよび感圧式描画サポート、カスタムツールパネル、設定のインポートとエクスポート。追加された拡張機能: レイヤーステートの記憶、中央からのアートボードの描画およびサイズ変更機能、各グリッドとアートワークの更新が一致するよう変更、スウォッチパネルでの塗り/ストローク制御へのアクセス、不透明度設定を制御するスライダー、レスポンシブ SVG ファイルを作成するためのオプション、SVG ファイルのピクセル調整済みラウンドトリップなど。修正事項: Alt/Option + スクロールによるズーム (Mac)、DWG ファイルエクスポート時のレイヤー構造の保持、Apple Magic Mouse 使用時のキーボードショートカット機能。</ja_JP>
        <ko_KR>활성 모퉁이, 새로운 연필 도구, 패스 세그먼트 모양 변경, Typekit  통합, Live Windows 7 및 8 HiDPI 지원, Windows 8 향상된 터치 및 압력 감지형 그리기, 사용자 정의 도구 패널, 설정 가져오기 및 내보내기. 추가 개선 사항: 레이어 상태 기억, 중앙에서 대지를 그리고 크기 조정하는 기능, 원근 그리드와 아트웍 업데이트 내용이 일치하도록 수정, 견본 패널에서 칠/획 컨트롤 접근, 불투명도 설정을 조절하는 슬라이더, 반응형 SVG 파일을 생성하는 옵션, SVG 파일의 픽셀 정렬 라운드 트리핑 등. 수정 사항: Mac에서 Alt/Option + 스크롤로 확대, DWG 파일을 내보낼 때 레이어 구조 유지, Apple Magic Mouse 사용 시 단축키 작동.</ko_KR>
        <nl_NL>Actieve hoeken, vernieuwd Potlood, Padsegment omvormen, integratie met Typekit, ondersteuning voor Windows 7 en 8 HiDPI, verbeterde touch-ondersteuning en drukgevoelige tekenondersteuning voor Windows 8, deelvenster Aangepaste gereedschappen, import- en exportinstellingen. Aanvullende verbeteringen: laagstatussen worden onthouden, tekengebied kan worden getekend en aangepast vanuit het midden, perspectiefraster en illustratie worden passend bijgewerkt, toegang tot vullings- en lijnopties vanuit het deelvenster Stalen, schuifregelaars voor het instellen van de dekking, de optie om responsieve SVG-bestanden te maken, uitlijnen op pixels en retourconversie is mogelijk bij SVG-bestanden, en meer. O.a. de volgende problemen zijn opgelost: zoomen op de Mac met Alt/Option + scrollen, behoud van de lagenstructuur bij het exporteren van DWG-bestanden, werkende sneltoetsen bij gebruik van de Magic Mouse van Apple.</nl_NL>
        <pl_PL>Obsługa funkcji Aktywne narożniki, całkowicie nowego narzędzia Ołówek, funkcji zmiany kształtu segmentów ścieżek. Integracja z czcionkami Typekit. Obsługa rozdzielczości HiDPI w systemach Windows 7 i 8. Usprawniona obsługa funkcji rysowania dotykowego i czułości nacisku podczas rysowania w systemie Windows 8. Panel narzędzi niestandardowych, importowanie i eksportowanie ustawień. Dodatkowe usprawnienia: zapamiętywanie stanów warstw, możliwość rysowania i zmiany rozmiaru przestrzeni roboczej od środka, modyfikowanie siatki perspektywy i aktualizowanie kompozycji tak, aby do siebie pasowały, dostęp do ustawień Wypełnienia i Obrysu w panelu Próbki, suwaki sterujące ustawieniami krycia, funkcja tworzenia reagujących plików SVG, wyrównane względem piksela pliki SVG w drodze do i z powrotem itd. Poprawki błędów obejmujące funkcję powiększania na Macu dostępną po naciśnięciu przycisku Alt/Option i poruszeniu kółkiem myszy, zachowanie struktury warstw w przypadku eksportu plików DWG, działanie skrótów klawiaturowych w trakcie korzystania z myszy Apple Magic Mouse.</pl_PL>
        <pt_BR>Cantos ativos, a nova ferramenta Lápis, Reformatar segmento de demarcador, integração com Typekit, compatibilidade com HiDPI no Windows 7 e 8, compatibilidade aprimorada com desenho por toque e sensível a pressão no Windows 8, painel Ferramentas personalizadas, importação e exportação de configurações. Aprimoramentos adicionais: gravação de estados de camadas, capacidade de desenhar e redimensionar extremidade da arte para o centro, modificar a grade de perspectiva e atualizações de arte para corresponder, acessar controles de preenchimento/traçado no painel Amostras, controles deslizantes de configurações de opacidade, opção para criação de arquivos SVG com envio de respostas, alinhamento de pixels em arquivos SVG e muito mais. Correções incluem: Alt/Option + rolagem para zoom no Mac, preservação da estrutura da camada ao exportar arquivos para DWG, funcionamento dos atalhos de teclado ao usar com Apple Magic Mouse.</pt_BR>
        <ru_RU>Динамические углы, новый инструмент "Карандаш", изменение формы сегмента контура, интеграция шрифтов Typekit, поддержка HiDPI для  Windows 7 и 8, улучшенная поддержка сенсорного рисования и контроля нажатия, настраиваемая панель инструментов, импорт и экспорт настроек. Дополнительные улучшения: сохранение состояний слоев, возможность вычерчивания и изменения размеров монтажной области из центра, изменение сетки перспективы с соответствующим обновлением иллюстрации, доступ к элементам управления заливкой/обводкой на панели "Образцы", ползунки для управления настройками прозрачности, возможность создания адаптивных файлов SVG, рисование контуров, выровненных по пикселам, для файлов SVG и др. Исправления: масштабирование на Mac с помощью прокрутки при нажатой клавише Alt/Option, сохранение структуры слоев при экспорте файлов DWG, поддержка комбинаций клавиш при использовании Apple Magic Mouse.</ru_RU>
        <sv_SE>Live-hörn, nytt pennverktyg, ändra form på bansegment, Typekit-integrering, stöd för Windows 7 &amp; 8 HiDPI, förbättrat stöd för touch och tryckkänslig ritning i Windows 8, anpassad verktygspanel, import och export av inställningar. Ytterligare förbättringar: bland annat sparande av lagerlägen, möjlighet att dra och omforma rityta från centrum, ändring av perspektivstödraster och teckningsuppdateringar för matchning, åtkomst till fyllnings- och streckkontroller i färgrutepanelen, reglage för opacitetsinställningar, alternativ för att skapa responsiva SVG-filer, pixeljusterad växling av SVG-filer. Korrigeringar omfattar: Alt/Option + rullning för zoomning på Mac, bibehållande av lagerstruktur vid export av DWG-filer, tangentbordskommandon fungerar med Apple Magic Mouse.</sv_SE>
        <tr_TR>Canlı Köşeler, Yepyeni Kurşun Kalem aracı, Yol Parçasının Yeniden Şekillendirilmesi, Typekit entegrasyonu, Windows 7 ve 8 HiDPI desteği, Windows 8 geliştirilmiş dokunma ve basınca duyarlı çizim desteği, Özel Araçlar paneli, Ayarları içe aktarma ve dışa aktarma. Ek geliştirmeler: Katman durumlarını hatırlama, çalışma yüzeyi çizme ve merkezden yeniden boyutlandırma özelliği, perspektif ızgaraları ve çalışma yüzeyi güncellemelerini düzenleyerek eşleşmelerini sağlama, Renk Örnekleri panelinde dolgu/kontur kontrollerine erişme, opaklık ayarlarını kontrol etmek için kaydırıcılar, hızlı yanıt verme performansına sahip SVG dosyaları oluşturma seçeneği, SVG dosyalarının pikselleri hizalanmış olarak tam düzenlenmesi ve daha fazlası. Düzeltmeler şunları içerir: Mac'de yakınlaştırma için Alt/Option tuşuna basılarak kaydırma yapılabilir, DWG dosyalarını dışa aktarırken katman yapısı korunur ve klavye kısayolları Apple Magic Mouse kullanırken çalıştırılabilir. </tr_TR>
        <uk_UA>Функції створення динамічних кутів, абсолютно новий інструмент створення нового олівця, можливість коригування сегментів контуру, інтеграція шрифтів Typekit, підтримка Windows 7 та 8 для екранів із надвисокою роздільною здатністю, підтримка вдосконаленої сенсорної технології Windows 8 та технології чутливості до натиску для малювання, функції створення власних панелей інструментів, імпорту та експорту налаштувань. Додаткові вдосконалення: функції запам'ятовування статусу шарів, можливості малювання і змінення розміру монтажної області з центру, коригування сітки перспективи та відповідного оновлення ілюстрацій, доступ до елементів редагування заливки/обведення з панелі зразків, повзунки для коригування налаштувань непрозорості, параметр створення залежних SVG-файлів, редагування SVG-файлів із вирівнюванням пікселів тощо. Інтегровані виправлення, серед яких: збільшення масштабу на комп'ютері Mac за допомогою комбінації клавіш Alt/Option + прокручування коліщатка миші, зберігання структури шару за експорту у DWG-файли, підтримка комбінацій клавіш за використання миші Apple Magic Mouse.</uk_UA>
        <zh_CN>实时转角、全新的铅笔工具、路径段整形、Typekit 集成、Windows 7 和 Windows 8 的 HiDPI 支持、Windows 8 中增强的触摸和压力感应绘图支持、自定工具面板、设置导入和导出。其他增强功能包括：记忆图层状态、从中心绘制画板和调整大小、修改透视网格和图稿更新以相符、访问色板面板中的填充/描边控件、使用滑块控制不透明度设置、创建响应 SVG 文件的选项、像素级 SVG 文件调整等等。错误修复包括：Mac 上按住 Alt/Option 并滚动以缩放、导出 DWG 文件时保留图层结构、使用 Apple Magic Mouse 时键盘快捷键可正常工作。</zh_CN>
        <zh_TW>即時尖角、全新的鉛筆工具、路徑區段改變外框、Typekit 整合、Windows 7 &amp; 8 HiDPI 支援、Windows 8 增強型觸控和壓感式繪圖支援、自訂工具面板、設定匯入和匯出。其他增強功能: 記憶圖層狀態、從工作區域中央繪製和調整大小的能力、修改透視格點和圖稿更新以符合、在「色票」面板中存取填色/筆畫控制項、滑桿控制不透明設定、可建立回應 SVG 檔案的選項、像素對齊的 SVG 檔案往返等等。修正包括: 在 Mac 上按住 Alt/Option 鍵並捲動以縮放顯示、轉存 DWG 檔案時保留圖層結構、使用 Apple Magic Mouse 時鍵盤快捷鍵仍可運作。</zh_TW>
		<en_AE>Live Corners, All-new Pencil tool, Path Segment Reshape, Typekit integration, Windows 7 &amp; 8 HiDPI support, Windows 8 enhanced touch and pressure-sensitive drawing support, Custom Tools panel, Settings import and export. Additional enhancements: Layer states remembered, ability to draw and resize artboard from center, modify perspective grid and artwork updates to match, access fill/stroke controls in Swatches panel, sliders to control opacity settings, option for creating responsive SVG files, pixel-aligned round-tripping of SVG files, and more. Fixes include: Alt/Option + scroll for zoom on Mac, preservation of layer structure when exporting DWG files, keyboard shortcuts work when using the Apple Magic Mouse.</en_AE>
		<en_IL>Live Corners, All-new Pencil tool, Path Segment Reshape, Typekit integration, Windows 7 &amp; 8 HiDPI support, Windows 8 enhanced touch and pressure-sensitive drawing support, Custom Tools panel, Settings import and export. Additional enhancements: Layer states remembered, ability to draw and resize artboard from center, modify perspective grid and artwork updates to match, access fill/stroke controls in Swatches panel, sliders to control opacity settings, option for creating responsive SVG files, pixel-aligned round-tripping of SVG files, and more. Fixes include: Alt/Option + scroll for zoom on Mac, preservation of layer structure when exporting DWG files, keyboard shortcuts work when using the Apple Magic Mouse.</en_IL>
    </Description>
    <AffectedChannels>
        <ChannelID>AdobeIllustrator17-mul_x64</ChannelID>
    </AffectedChannels>
    <InstallFiles>
    <File RIBSBased="1">
      <Name>
        
      </Name>
      <Type>
        
      </Type>
      <ExecutableName>
        
      </ExecutableName>
      <Size>
        
      </Size>
      
    </File>
  </InstallFiles>
    <NeedsReboot>false</NeedsReboot>

  
  
  
  
  
  
  <UpdatePayloadID>{2A900D2C-3DF0-47E9-81F4-9BC565B93AFA}</UpdatePayloadID>
  <OwningPayloadID>{CCDC3E53-DF98-434F-821A-C253C61DA2CD}</OwningPayloadID>
  <ConflictingProcesses>
    <Process processType="Adobe" blocking="1">^[Ii][Ll][Ll][Uu][Ss][Tt][Rr][Aa][Tt][Oo][Rr]\.[Ee][Xx][Ee]</Process>
    <Process processType="Adobe" blocking="1">^[Cc][Rr][Aa][Ss][Hh][Rr][Ee][Pp][Oo][Rr][Tt][Ee][Rr]App\.[Ee][Xx][Ee]</Process>
  </ConflictingProcesses>
</Manifest>
